Guide to the Julio Elizalde Papers [Guía a los escritos de Julio Elizalde], 1973-2007 LATINAMER.2013.01
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Writings, 1972-2007; I.
  - Writings, January-June 1990 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Un mensaje urgente (Dividido en incisos), Para: General Dynamic Corp., Boeing Co., McDonnell Corp. [An Urgent Message (Divided in Sections), To: General Dynamic Corp., Boeing Co., McDonnell Corp.], 17 de abril, 1990 [April 17, 1990]; 22.; 4 pages
    - Mensaje decisivo #3 (Dividido en incisos), Para: General Dynamic Corp., Boeing Co., McDonnell Corp. [Decisive Message #3 (Divided in Sections), To: General Dynamic Corp., Boeing Co., McDonnell Corp.], 19 de abril, 1990 [April 19, 1990]; 23.; 5 pages
    - Mensaje decisivo #10 (Dividido en incisos), Para: General Dynamic Corp., Boeing Co., McDonnell Corp. [Decisive Message #10 (Divided in Sections), To: General Dynamic Corp., Boeing Co., McDonnell Corp.], 20 de abril, 1990 [April 20, 1990]; 24.; 4 pages
    - Mensaje decisivo #8 (Dividido en incisos), Para: General Dynamic Corp., Boeing Co., McDonnell Corp. [Decisive Message #8 (Divided in Sections), To: General Dynamic Corp., Boeing Co., McDonnell Corp.], 27 de abril, 1990 [April 27, 1990]; 25.; 4 pages
    - Un mensaje al Buró Federal de Investigaciones F.B.I. [A Message to the Federal Bureau of Investigations F.B.I.], 22 de abril, 1990 [April 22, 1990]; 26.; 4 pages
    - Mensaje decisivo #9 (Dividido en incisos), Para: General Dynamic Corp., Boeing Co., McDonnell Corp. [Decisive Message #9 (Divided in Sections), To: General Dynamic Corp., Boeing Co., McDonnell Corp.], 28 de abril, 1990; 27.; 3 pages
    - Mensajes extraordinarios (Dividido en incisos). Otra visita a Federal Plaza [Extraordinary Messages (Divided in Sections). Another Visit to the Federal Plaza], 18 de mayo, 1990 [May 18, 1990]; 28.; 2 pages
    - Documentos extraordinarios (Dividido en incisos) [Extraordinary Documents (Divided in Sections)], 10 de junio, 1990 [June 10, 1990]; 29.; 4 pages
    - Nota [Note], 11 de junio, 1990 [June 11, 1990]; 30.; 2 pages
    - Mensajes extraordinarios: Proposición [Extraordinary Messages: Proposition], 15 de junio, 1990 [June 15, 1990]; 31.; 2 pages
    - Observaciones [Observations], 27 de junio, 1990 [June 27, 1990]; 32.; 1 page
  - Writings, July-December 1990 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Mensajes trascendentales [Transcendental Messages], 9 de julio, 1990 [July 9, 1990]; 1.; 3 pages
    - Reflexiones [Reflections], 12 de julio, 1990 [July 12, 1990]; 2.; 5 pages
    - Reflexiones [Reflections], 14 de julio, 1990 [July 14, 1990]; 3.; 5 pages
    - Reflexiones [Reflections], 27 de julio, 1990 [July 27, 1990]; 4.; 4 pages
    - Reflexiones [Reflections], 27 de julio, 1990 [July 27, 1990]; 5.; 4 pages
    - Nota [Note], 28 de julio, 1990 [July 28, 1990]; 6.; 1 page
    - Desde la cima del drama mundial: Fuerza vital e histórica determinante [At the Heights of World Drama: Vital Force and Decisive History], 9 de julio, 1990 [July 9, 1990]; 7.; 3 pages
    - Mensaje urgente #4 [Urgent Message #4], 2 de agosto, 1990; 8.; 2 pages
    - Aclaración [Clarification], 18 de agosto, 1990 [August 18, 1990]; 9.; 1 page
    - Desde la cima del drama mundial: Una visión global de la crisis en el Medio Oriente [At the Heights of World Conflict: A Global Vision of the Crisis in the Middle East], 22 de agosto, 1990 [August 22, 1990]; 10.; 8 pages
    - Breves reflexiones [Brief Reflections], 27 de agosto, 1990 [August 27, 1990]; 11.; 1 page
    - Breves reflexiones [Brief Reflections], 27 de agosto, 1990 [August 27, 1990]; 12.; 3 pages
    - Breves reflexiones [Brief Reflections], 30 de agosto, 1990 [August 30, 1990]; 13.; 3 pages
    - Reflexiones [Reflections], 31 de agosto, 1990 [August 31, 1990]; 14.; 3 pages
    - Desde la cima del drama mundial: Un mensaje urgente al general H. Norman Schwarzkopf, Comandante Supremo de las tropas americanas en Arabia Saudita [At the Heights of World Conflict: An Urgent Message to the General H. Norman Schwarzkopf, Supreme Commander of the American Troops in Saudi Arabia], 1 de septiembre, 1990 [September 1, 1990]; 15.; 5 pages
    - Desde la cima del drama mundial: Un mensaje urgente al general H. Norman Schwarzkopf, Comandante Supremo de las tropas americanas en Arabia Saudita [At the Heights of World Conflict: An Urgent Message to the General H. Norman Schwarzkopf, Supreme Commander of the American Troops in Saudi Arabia], 2 de septiembre, 1990 [September 2, 1990]; 16.; 6 pages
    - Reflexiones [Reflections], 13 de septiembre, 1990 [September 13, 1990]; 17.; 5 pages
    - Reflexiones [Reflections], 26 de septiembre, 1990 [September 26, 1990]; 18.; 4 pages
    - Reflexiones [Reflections], 29 de septiembre, 1990 [September 29, 1990]; 19.; 4 pages
    - Nota (Dividida en incisos) [Note (Divided in Sections)], 3 de octubre, 1990 [October 3, 1990]; 20.; 2 pages
    - Nota (Dividida en incisos) [Note (Divided in Sections)], 5 de octubre, 1990 [October 5, 1990]; 21.; 3 pages
    - Nota (Dividida en incisos) [Note (Divided in Sections)], 17 de octubre, 1990 [October 17, 1990]; 22.; 3 pages
    - Nota [Note], 24 de octubre, 1990 [October 24, 1990]; 23.; 2 pages
    - Mensajes extraordinarios (Dividido en incisos) [Extraordinary Messages (Divided in Sections)], 6 de noviembre, 1990; 24.; 3 pages
    - La Crisis Mundial [The World Crisis], 17 de noviembre, 1990 [November 17, 1990]; 25.; 5 pages
    - Reflexiones sobre la crisis mundial [Reflections About the World Crisis], 19 de noviembre, 1990 [November 19, 1990]; 26.; 5 pages
    - Mensajes políticos trascendentales [Transcendental Political Messages], 20 de noviembre, 1990 [November 20, 1990]; 27.; 4 pages
    - Nota muy, muy enérgica [Very, Very Energetic Note], 21 de noviembre, 1990 [November 21, 1990]; 28.; 3 pages
    - Mensajes políticos extraordinarios [Extraordinary Political Messages], 26 de noviembre, 1990 [November 26, 1990]; 29.; 2 pages
    - Grandes mensajes políticos [Grand Political Messages], 30 de noviembre, 1990 [November 30, 1990]; 30.; 2 pages
    - Mensajes políticos trascendentales [Transcendental Political Messages], 9 de diciembre, 1990 [December 9, 1990]; 31.; 5 pages
    - Un mensaje urgente al Supremo Leadership [An Urgent Message to the Supreme Leadership], 10 de diciembre, 1990 [December 10, 1990]; 32.; 1 page
    - Sin título [Untitled], 13 de diciembre, 1990 [December 13, 1990]; 33.; 1 page
    - Mensajes políticos trascendentales: Unas observaciones dirigidas a la Comisión Investigadora del Navy [Transcendental Political Messages: Some Observations Directed at the Commission of Inquiry of the Navy], 24 de diciembre, 1990 [December 24, 1990]; 34.; 3 pages
    - Mensajes políticos trascendentales [Transcendental Political Messages], 27 de diciembre, 1990 [December 27, 1990]; 36.; 3 pages
    - Mensajes políticos trascendentales: La Casa Blanca, ¿insiste en apartar el rostro de la realidad? [Transcendental Political Messages: Does the White House Insist on Turning Away the Face of Reality?], 28 de diciembre, 1990 [December 28, 1990]; 35.; 3 pages
    - Mensajes políticos trascendentales: Documentos de oro [Transcendental Political Messages: Documents of Gold], 29 de diciembre, 1990 [December 29, 1990]; 37.; 3 pages
  - Writings, January-June 1991 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Nota: La hora de verdad [Note: The Hour of Truth], 2 de enero, 1991 [January 2, 1991]; 1.; 1 page
    - Un mensaje urgente [An Urgent Message], 8 de enero, 1991 [January 8, 1991]; 2.; 2 pages
    - El drama mundial y la crisis americana [World Conflict and the American Crisis], 14 de enero, 1991 [January 14, 1991]; 3.; 3 pages
    - Horas decisivas [Decisive Hours], 16 de enero, 1991 [January 16, 1991]; 4.; 3 pages
    - Horas decisivas [Decisive Hours], 25 de enero, 1991 [January 25, 1991]; 5.; 3 pages
    - Nota muy enérgica #2 (Dividida en incisos) [Very Energetic Note #2 (Divided in Sections)], 6 de febrero, 1991 [February 6, 1991]; 6.; 2 pages
    - Horas decisivas (Dividida en incisos) [Decisive Hours (Divided in Sections)], 13 de febrero, 1991 [February 13, 1991]; 7.; 3 pages
    - Un mensaje especial a Alemania [A Special Message to Germany], 15 de febrero, 1991 [February 15, 1991]; 8.; 5 pages
    - Horas decisivas: El plan [Decisive Hours: The Plan], 20 de febrero, 1991 [February 20, 1991]; 9.; 2 pages
    - Horas decisivas [Decisive Hours], 22 de febrero, 1991 [February 22, 1991]; 10.; 3 pages
    - Horas decisivas [Decisive Hours], 2 de marzo, 1991 [March 2, 1991]; 11.; 4 pages
    - Horas decisivas [Decisive Hours], 3 de marzo, 1991 [March 3, 1991]; 12.; 5 pages
    - Nota [Note], 12 de abril, 1991 [April 12, 1991]; 13.; 1 page
    - Mensajes especiales al supremo leadership: Un conflicto eterno [Special Messages to the Supreme Leadership: An Eternal Conflict], 15 de abril, 1991 [April 15, 1991]; 14.; 3 pages
    - Mensajes especiales al supremo leadership: Grito de alarma [Special Messages to the Supreme Leadership: Cry of Alarm], 17 de abril, 1991 [April 17, 1991]; 15.; 2 pages
    - Mensajes especiales al Supremo Leadership: Las flores sin agua se secan [Special Messages to the Supreme Leadership: Flowers, without water, dry up], 18 de abril, 1991 [April 18, 1991]; 16.; 1 page
    - Mensajes especiales al Supremo Leadership [Special Messages to the Supreme Leadership], 20 de abril, 1991 [April 20, 1991]; 17.; 2 pages
    - Mensajes especiales al Supremo Leadership [Special Messages to the Supreme Leadership], 20 de abril, 1991 [April 20, 1991]; 18.; 2 pages
    - Momentos decisivos en la vida de un hombre [Decisive Moments in the Life of a Man], 24 de abril, 1991 [April 24, 1991]; 19.; 3 pages
    - Otro mensaje al Supremo Leadership [Another Message to the Supreme Leadership], 14 de mayo, 1991 [May 14, 1991]; 20.; 2 pages
    - Mensajes al Supremo Leadership [Messages to the Supreme Leadership], 16 de mayo, 1991 [May 16, 1991]; 21.; 5 pages
    - Mensajes especiales al Supremo Leadership [Special Messages to the Supreme Leadership], 17 de mayo, 1991 [May 17, 1991]; 22.; 5 pages
    - Un mensaje especial al Supremo Leadership [A Special Message to the Supreme Leadership], 29 de mayo, 1991 [May 29, 1991]; 23.; 1 page
    - Reflexiones: Evidencias de una gigantesca victoria, política, intelectual, moral. Las grandes sociedades se colapsan por razones internas, jamás por motivos externos. Baker y Bush no desean ver la realidad [Reflections, Evidence of a Gigantic Political, Intellectual, Moral. Great Societies Collapse for Internal Reasons, Never for External Reasons. Baker y Bush Do Not Desire to See the Reality], 31 de mayo, 1991 [May 31, 1991]; 24.; 4 pages
    - Reflexiones: Un delicadisimo conflicto moral. El delito de alta traición y la desintegración de los Estados Unidos. Groseramente, Bush, Baker, Cheney distorsionan a la historia [Reflections: A Very Delicate Moral Conflict. The Crime of High Treason and the Disintegration of the United States. Grossly, Bush, Baker, Cheney Distort History], 1 de junio, 1991 [June 1, 1991]; 25.; 4 pages
    - Mensajes especiales al Supremo Leadership [Special Messages to the Supreme Leadership], 6 de junio, 1991 [June 6, 1991]; 26.; 4 pages
  - Writings, July-December 1991 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Nota #3: Final [Note #3: Final], 18 de julio, 1991 [July 18, 1991]; 1.; 5 pages
    - Reflexiones [Reflections], 19 de julio, 1991 [July 19, 1991]; 2.; 4 pages
    - Un mensaje especial a las tres instituciones privadas [A Special Message to the Three Private Institutions], 21 de julio, 1991 [July 21, 1991]; 3.; 5 pages
    - Intitulado [Untitled], 28 de julio, 1991 [July 28, 1991]; 4.; 4 pages
    - Un mensaje especial a los servicios de inteligencia del Navy [A Special Message to the Intelligence Services of the Navy], 4 de agosto, 1991 [August 4, 1991]; 5.; 4 pages
    - Mensajes extraordinarios al Supremo Leadership [Extraordinary Messages to the Supreme Leadership], 15 de agosto, 1991 [August 15, 1991]; 6.; 4 pages
    - Un mensaje a Georg, mi amigo de la biblioteca de la calle 40 y 5ta. avenida [A Message to Georg, My Friend From the Library at 40th Street and 5th Avenue], 18 de agosto, 1991 [August 18, 1991]; 7.; 3 pages
    - Grandes mensajes al Supremo Leadership [Grand Messages to the Supreme Leadership], 22 de agosto, 1991 [August 22, 1991]; 8.; 4 pages
    - Grandes mensajes al Supremo Leadership: Introducción especial específicamente dirigida al leadership [Grand Messages to the Supreme Leadership: Special Introduction Specifically Addressed to the Leadership], 24 de agosto, 1991 [August 24, 1991]; 9.; 7 pages
    - Grandes mensajes al Supremo Leadership [Grand Messages to the Supreme Leadership], 4 de septiembre, 1991 [September 4, 1991]; 10.; 6 pages
    - Grandes mensajes al Supremo Leadership [Grand Messages to the Supreme Leadership], 6 de septiembre, 1991 [September 6, 1991]; 11.; 5 pages
    - Grandes mensajes al Supremo Leadership [Grand Messages to the Supreme Leadership], 10 de septiembre, 1991 [September 10, 1991]; 12.; 5 pages
    - Otro mensaje a las tres instituciones privadas [Another Message to the Three Private Institutions], 20 de septiembre, 1991 [September 20, 1991]; 13.; 4 pages
    - Mensajes decisivos al Supremo Leadership [Decisive Messages to the Supreme Leadership], 23 de septiembre, 1991 [September 23, 1991]; 14.; 5 pages
    - Grandes mensajes al Supremo Leadership [Grand Messages to the Supreme Leadership], 26 de septiembre, 1991 [September 26, 1991]; 15.; 4 pages
    - Nota [Note], 23 de octubre, 1991 [October 23, 1991]; 16.; 3 pages
    - Mensajes decisivos [Decisive Messages], 27 de octubre, 1991; 17.; 5 pages
    - Nota [Note], 23 de octubre, 1991 [October 23, 1991]; 18.; 3 pages
    - Mensajes decisivos [Decisive Messages], 27 de octubre, 1991 [October 27, 1991]; 19.; 5 pages
    - Un mensaje especial [A Special Message], 4 de noviembre, 1991 [November 4, 1991]; 20.; 5 pages
    - Nota [Note], 21 de noviembre, 1991 [November 21, 1991]; 21.; 2 pages
    - Un mensaje urgente al Supremo Leadership [An Urgent Message to the Supreme Leadership], 5 de diciembre, 1991 [December 5, 1991]; 22.; 2 pages
    - Horas decisivas [Decisive Hours], 6 de diciembre, 1991 [December 6, 1991]; 23.; 6 pages
  - Writings, January-May 1992 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Segundo mensaje desesperado al Supremo Leadership [Second Desperate Message to the Supreme Leadership], 11 de enero, 1992 [January 11, 1992]; 1.; 4 pages
    - Mensajes especiales al Supremo Leadership [Special Messages to the Supreme Leadership], 19 de enero, 1992 [January 19, 1992]; 2.; 5 pages
    - Mensajes especiales al Supremo Leadership [Special Messages to the Supreme Leadership], 23 de enero, 1992 [January 23, 1992]; 3.; 5 pages
    - Horas decisivas: The Hour of the Truth [Decisive Hours: The Hour of the Truth], 2 de febrero, 1992 [February 2, 1992]; 4.; 2 pages
    - Nota [Note], 3 de febrero, 1992 [February 3, 1992]; 5.; 1 page
    - Mensajes decisivos [Decisive Messages], 4 de febrero, 1992 [February 4, 1992]; 6.; 4 pages
    - Un mensaje especial al Supremo Leadership [A Special Message to the Supreme Leadership], 6 de febrero, 1992 [February 6, 1992]; 7.; 4 pages
    - Observaciones [Observations], 15 de febrero, 1992 [February 15, 1992]; 8.; 2 pages
    - Mensajes especiales al Supremo Leadership [Special Messages to the Supreme Leadership], 20 de febrero, 1992 [February 20, 1992]; 9.; 2 pages
    - Horas decisivas [Decisive Hours], 24 de febrero, 1992 [February 24, 1992]; 10.; 4 pages
    - Segunda mensaje a Alemania, la Alemania inmortal [Second Message to Germany, the Immortal Germany], 7 de marzo, 1992 [March 7, 1992]; 11.; 5 pages
    - Horas decisivas (Dividido en incisos) [Decisive Hours (Divided in Sections)], 20 de marzo, 1992 [March 20, 1992]; 12.; 5 pages
    - Horas decisivas (Dividido en incisos) [Decisive Hours (Divided in Sections)], 21 de marzo, 1992 [March 21, 1992]; 13.
    - Mensaje final (Dividido en incisos) [Final Message (Divided in Sections)], 3 de abril, 1992 [April 3, 1992]; 14.; 6 pages
    - Minutos decisivos [Decisive Minutes], 9 de abril, 1992 [April 9, 1992]; 15.; 6 pages
    - Horas decisivas (Dividido en incisos) [Decisive Hours (Divided in Sections)], 15 de abril, 1992 [April 15, 1992]; 16.; 5 pages
    - Horas decisivas (Dividido en incisos) [Decisive Hours (Divided in Sections)], 19 de abril, 1992 [April 19, 1992]; 17.; 3 pages
    - Mensajes especiales al Supremo Leadership [Special Messages to the Supreme Leadership], 10 de mayo, 1992 [May 10, 1992]; 18.; 3 pages
    - Mensajes especiales en horas decisivas [Special Messages in Decisive Hours], 13 de mayo, 1992 [May 13, 1992]; 19.; 4 pages
    - Mensajes especiales en horas decisivas [Special Messages in Decisive Hours], 14 de mayo, 1992 [May 14, 1992]; 20.; 3 pages
    - Horas decisivas [Decisive Hours], 28 de mayo, 1992 [May 28, 1992]; 21.; 4 pages
  - Writings, June-December 1992 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Mensajes de angustia #4 [Messages of Anguish #4], 19 de junio, 1992 [June 19, 1992]; 1.; 5 pages
    - Mensajes especiales [Special Messages], 25 de junio, 1992 [June 25, 1992]; 2.; 5 pages
    - Mensajes especiales [Special Messages], 28 de junio, 1992 [June 28, 1992]; 3.; 4 pages
    - Horas decisivas [Decisive Hours], 29 de junio, 1992 [June 29, 1992]; 4.; 3 pages
    - Un mensaje especial [A Special Message], 2 de julio, 1992 [July 2, 1992]; 5.; 3 pages
    - Reflexiones [Reflections], 8 de julio, 1992 [July 8, 1992]; 6.; 4 pages
    - Notas [Notes], 8 de julio, 1992 [July 8, 1992]; 7.; 2 pages
    - Mensajes decisivos [Decisive Messages], 9 de julio, 1992 [July 9, 1992]; 8.; 5 pages
    - Horas decisivas [Decisive Hours], 10 de julio, 1992 [July 10, 1992]; 9.; 4 pages
    - Horas decisivas (Dividida en incisos) [Decisive Hours (Divided in Sections)], 11 de julio, 1992 [July 11, 1992]; 10.; 4 pages
    - Horas decisivas [Decisive Hours], 12 de julio, 1992 [July 12, 1992]; 11.; 4 pages
    - Un mensaje especial: Curriculum Vitae (Résumé) [A Special Message: Curriculum Vitae (Résumé)], 24 de agosto, 1992 [August 24, 1992]; 12.; 7 pages
    - Hora Decisivas: El paso inmediato es la normalización [Decisive Hours: The Immediate Step is Normalization], 2 de octubre, 1992 [October 2, 1992]; 13.; 3 pages
    - La solución tiene que brotar ahora, inmediatamente. Ross Perot [The Solution Has to Emerge Now, Immediately. Ross Perot], 6 de noviembre, 1992 [November 6, 1992]; 14.; 3 pages
    - Un mini-mensaje: Otro golpe, en este caso devastador, próximo a ser inasimilable [A Mini-Message: Another Blow, in This Devastating Case, Nears to Become Unassimilable], 15 de noviembre, 1992 [November 15, 1992]; 15.; 3 pages
    - Mensaje urgente #2 al Supremo Leadership [Urgent Message #2 to the Supreme Leadership], 17 de noviembre, 1992 [November 17, 1992]; 16.; 4 pages
    - Mensaje urgente #4 al Supremo Leadership [Urgent Message #4 to the Supreme Leadership], 19 de noviembre, 1992 [November 19, 1992]; 17.; 3 pages
    - La hora de la verdad (Segunda parte) [The Hour of Truth (Second Part)], 4 de diciembre, 1992; 18.; 4 pages
  - Writings, January-April 1993 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Mensaje desesperado #3 y final al Supremo Leadership [Desperate and Final Message #3 to the Supreme Leadership], 14 de enero, 1993 [January 14, 1993]; 1.; 5 pages
    - Post Scriptum #2 a los dos mensajes desesperados al Supremo Leadership [Post Scriptum #2 to the Two Desperate Messages to the Supreme Leadership], 16 de enero, 1993 [January 16, 1993]; 2.; 5 pages
    - Mensaje especial #2 al Supremo Leadership [Special Message #2 to the Supreme Leadership], 19 de enero, 1993 [January 19, 1993]; 3.; 5 pages
    - Mensajes muy delicados al Supremo Leadership [Very Delicate Messages to the Supreme Leadership], 27 de enero, 1993 [January 27, 1993]; 4.; 4 pages
    - Mensajes muy delicados al Supremo Leadership [Very Delicate Messages to the Supreme Leadership], 28 de enero, 1993 [January 28, 1993]; 5.; 5 pages
    - Desde la cima del drama socio-político mundial [At the Heights of Socio-political World Drama], 31 de enero, 1993 [January 31, 1993]; 6.; 6 pages
    - Horas decisivas [Decisive Hours], 2 de febrero, 1993 [February 2, 1993]; 7.; 7 pages
    - Horas decisivas [Decisive Hours], 4 de febrero, 1993 [February 4, 1993]; 8.; 6 pages
    - Tercer mensaje a los servicios de inteligencia del Navy [Third Message to the Intelligence Services of the Navy], 24 de febrero, 1993 [February 24, 1993]; 9.; 2 pages
    - Mensaje especial #3 al Supremo Leadership [Special Message #3 to the Supreme Leadership], 6 de marzo, 1993 [March 6, 1993]; 10.; 5 pages
    - Mensaje especial #4 al Supremo Leadership [Special Message #4 to the Supreme Leadership], 8 de marzo, 1993 [March 8, 1993]; 11.; 4 pages
    - Mensaje especial #6 al Supremo Leadership [Special Message #6 to the Supreme Leadership], 9 de marzo, 1993 [March 9, 1993]; 12.; 4 pages
    - Mensaje especial #16 al Supremo Leadership [Special Message #16 to the Supreme Leadership], 20 de marzo, 1993; 13.; 6 pages
    - Mensaje especial #18 al Supremo Leadership [Special Message #18 to the Supreme Leadership], 22 de marzo, 1993; 14.; 4 pages
    - Mensaje especial #21 al Supremo Leadership [Special Message #21 to the Supreme Leadership], 25 de marzo, 1993 [March 25, 1993]; 15.; 5 pages
    - Mensaje especial #23 al Supremo Leadership [Special Message #23 to the Supreme Leadership], 27 de marzo, 1993 [March 27, 1993]; 16.; 5 pages
    - Horas decisivas #2 [Decisive Hours #2], 29 de marzo, 1993; 17.; 5 pages
    - Un mensaje desesperado al Supremo Leadership (Dividido en incisos) [A Desperate Message to the Supreme Leadership (Divided in Sections)], 12 de abril, 1993 [April 12, 1993]; 18.; 3 pages
    - Mensaje desesperado #2 al Supremo Leadership (Dividido en incisos) [Desperate Message #2 to the Supreme Leadership (Divided in Sections)], 13 de abril, 1993 [April 13, 1993]; 19.; 4 pages
  - Writings, May-August 1993 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Un mensaje especial al Supremo Leadership (Segunda parte) [A Special Message to the Supreme Leadership (Second Part)], 13 de mayo, 1993 [May 13, 1993]; 1.; 6 pages
    - Mensaje especial al Leadership [Special Message to the Leadership], 14 de mayo, 1993 [May 14, 1993]; 2.; 6 pages
    - Mensajes especiales al Supremo Leadership [Special Messages to the Supreme Leadership], 20 de mayo, 1993 [May 20, 1993]; 3.; 5 pages
    - Mensajes especiales al Supremo Leadership [Special Messages to the Supreme Leadership], 21 de mayo, 1993 [May 21, 1993]; 4.; 5 pages
    - Mensajes especiales al Supremo Leadership [Special Messages to the Supreme Leadership], 22 de mayo, 1993 [May 22, 1993]; 5.; 4 pages
    - Mensajes especiales al Supremo Leadership [Special Messages to the Supreme Leadership], 24 de mayo, 1993 [May 24, 1993]; 6.; 4 pages
    - Horas decisivas [Decisive Hours], 26 de mayo, 1993 [May 26, 1993]; 7.; 5 pages
    - Horas decisivas [Decisive Hours], 27 de mayo, 1993 [May 27, 1993]; 8.; 5 pages
    - Horas decisivas [Decisive Hours], 28 de mayo, 1993 [May 28, 1993]; 9.; 5 pages
    - Análisis: Agripina y Nerón no han muerto, ellos viven [Analysis: Agripina y Neron Have Not Died, They Are Living], 4 de junio, 1993 [June 4, 1993]; 10.; 6 pages
    - Mensajes decisivos [Decisive Messages], 5 de junio, 1993 [June 5, 1993]; 11.; 2 pages
    - Un análisis especial [A Special Analysis], 6 de junio, 1993 [June 6, 1993]; 12.; 6 pages
    - Análisis especial #3 [Special Analysis #3], 8 de junio, 1993 [June 8, 1993]; 13.; 6 pages
    - Análisis especial #7 [Special Analysis #7], 12 de junio, 1993 [June 12, 1993]; 14.; 5 pages
    - Análisis especial #8 [Special Analysis #8], 13 de junio, 1993 [June 13, 1993]; 15.; 5 pages
    - Análisis especial #8 [Special Analysis #8], 14 de junio, 1993 [June 14, 1993]; 16.; 2 pages
    - Nota Urgente [Urgent Note], 17 de junio, 1993 [June 17, 1993]; 17.; 2 pages
    - Análisis especial #15 [Special Analysis #15], 24 de junio, 1993 [June 24, 1993]; 18.; 4 pages